Contact

7389126962 (Mobile) anmol3540@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anmol-tomer (LinkedIn) github.com/AnmolTomer (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Machine Learning **Cloud Computing**

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Hindi (Native or Bilingual) German

Certifications

Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Foundation

Elastic Cloud Infrastructure: Scaling and Automation

Introduction to Python

Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Core Services

Reliable Cloud Infrastructure: Design and Process

Anmol Tomer

ML Intern at Nokia, Member at VIThink, VIT Chennai Electronics and Computer Science Engineer

Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

Summary

Machine Learning | Data Analytics | DevOps

Competencies: Python, C++, C, JavaScript, Machine Learning, Cloud Computing

I am a tech freak and someone who stays constantly updated with the recent tools and trends in the tech industry. I love to pick apart a motherboard and see how all the pieces fit together in my free time.

My intellectual curiosity drives me to find answers to the most pressing questions.

Applying my programming skills to solve real world problems in an efficient manner is what excites me.

I am a curious learner, and I am always very academically oriented and focused on maximizing my learning experiences.

See my Github repositories at https://github.com/AnmolTomer My twitter handle is anmol_tomer_cc

Email address: anmol3540@gmail.com

Experience

VIThink Member September 2018 - Present Chennai Area, India

We are a student run research and development group, with the stated aim of promoting interdisciplinary AI research among undergrads. We are tinkering with all things AI -- from vanilla Machine Learning to Generative Adversarial Networks, and everything in between. VIThink was founded in the summer of 2018 by the visionary Dr. Susan Elias with a team of 15 passionate undergrads at the Vellore Institute of Technology, Chennai Campus. United by the dream of intelligent machines, and armed with a zealous thirst for

Page 1 of 3

knowledge, we have set out to create, to apply, to contribute and to think. Remember: the wittier you are, the more respected you will be.

Nokia Intern May 2019 - May 2019 (1 month) Chennai Area, India

Intern at Nokia Solutions and Network in Machine Learning and Data Analytics Team.

VITCMUN 2019
Web Developer
December 2018 - March 2019 (4 months)
Chennai Area, India

Was part of VITCMUN Tech Team to develop a smart website which can give intelligent feedback to the users based upon the inputs given by them and make a responsive website to cater all the technical needs of the MUN application process.

MUNVERSE: A robust conversation app to replace the chit system in Model United Nations build over node with socket.

Role primiarily consisted of being a developer in tech team where product on which we were working on was a chat app made for use in Model United Nations (MUN), mock parliaments and is ideal for multiple MUN committees. It is made with the latest standards, front-end is made using Bulma js and backend comprises of NodeJS server, MongoDB as primary database and authentication is being done using PassportJS.

This system is capable of being run completely offline.{The recipients ideally connect to a local host address where a NodeJS server along with MongoDB is running for exchange of messages.) Chat app is easy to deploy, light and code has been written with specific standards so users can adapt and change it as per their custom requirements for different events.

Education

Vellore Institute of Technology
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electronics and Computer
Engineering · (2018 - 2022)

Free Code Camp

Engineer's Degree, Full Stack Web Development Certification · (2017 - 2018)